Guide to the E. Ethelbert Miller papers, 1936-2021, bulk 1962-2018 MS2215
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Ethelbert Miller materials, 1962-2018; 1940-2021; Series 1; Miller, E. Ethelbert
  - Poet files, 1969-2009; 1969-2020; Series 1 Subseries 2
    - Winslow, Rosemary, 2007-2008; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 125, Folder 2)
    - Winston, Michael, 1970-1983, 1990; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 121, Folder 4)
    - Wirth, Thomas, 1983; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 121, Folder 5)
    - Wise, Karsonya E., 1993-1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 121, Folder 6)
    - Woldemariam, Befekadu Bekele, 2008; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 121, Folder 8)
    - Wonder, A. Small, 1995, 2001; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 121, Folder 9)
    - Wood, Debbie, 1976-1983; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 121, Folder 10)
    - Wood, J.A., 1994-1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 121, Folder 11)
    - Woodbury, G. Ann, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 121, Folder 12)
    - Woodward, Veretta, 1988; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 122, Folder 1)
    - Woolford, Pamela, 1996-1997; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 122, Folder 2)
    - Wray, Clyde, 1994-1996; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 122, Folder 3)
    - Wray, Ronald, 1994, 2001; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 122, Folder 4)
    - Wright, Alta, 1983-1989; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 122, Folder 5)
    - Wright, Jay, 1972-1983, 1995-2000; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 122, Folder 6)
    - Wright, Stephen: works by, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Wright, Stephen: correspondence, 1992-2000 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Writers' Union, 1981-1982; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 175, Folder 2)
    - Wronsky, Gail, 1983-1991; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 122, Folder 7)
    - Wyche, Lisa, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 122, Folder 8)
    - Wynter, Sylvia, 1981-1982; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 122, Folder 9)
    - Wysham, Daphne, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 122, Folder 10)
    - Ya, Salaam: corespondence, works by, undated (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Yadav, Anu, 2004-2006; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 172, Folder 9)
    - Yamada, Mitsuye, 1989-1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - Yamhure, Laura C., 1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 123, Folder 2)
    - Yao (Hoke S. Glover III), 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 123, Folder 3)
    - Yoder, Jon, 1990-1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 123, Folder 4)
    - Yorker, Karmen, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 123, Folder 5)
    - Young, Al, 1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 123, Folder 6)
    - Young, Cheron, 1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 123, Folder 7)
    - Young, Ivy, 1981; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 123, Folder 8)
    - Young, Kevin, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 123, Folder 9)
    - Yun, Lisa Li Shen, 2002; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 123, Folder 10)
    - Zadravec, Katharine, 1989; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 123, Folder 11)
    - Zarco, Cyn, 1984-1986; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 123, Folder 12)
    - Zaqtan, Ghassan, 1997; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 125, Folder 3)
    - Zimmerman, Irene, 1991-1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 123, Folder 13)
    - Zu Bolton, Y.: promotional material, correspondence, 1975-1998 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Zu Bolton, Y.: postcards, correspondence, 1975-1993 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Zu Bolton, Y: resume, undated (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Zu Bolton, Y: articles, 2006 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Zu Bolton, Y: works by (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Zu Bolton, Ahmos: miscellaneous, 2005-2006 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Zu-Bolton II, Ahmos (1/3), 1975; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 123, Folder 14)
    - Zu-Bolton II, Ahmos (2/3), 2001; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 123, Folder 15)
    - Zu-Bolton II, Ahmos (3/3), 2001; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 123, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous Artist Materials, 1984-2010; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 171, Folder 8)
    - Poems, Undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 178, Folder 1)
    - Various Arts Materials, 1998-2015; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 173, Folder 6)
    - Various Poets/Authors, 1977, 1993, 2004, 2011, 2014, 2020; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 200, Folder 9)
  - Publications, 1968-2021; Series 1 Subseries 3
    This subseries contains magazines, newspapers, journals and other materials where works of Ethelbert Miller have been published, by name of publication. This subseries also contains works and publications collected by Ethelbert Miller that may document Black poetry or other subjects, and that are not found in many other respositories. The material dates from 1968-2021.
    This series is loosely arranged chronologically--the chronology starts over with boxes from newer additions.
    - The Black Collegian, 1971 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Transitions, 1972 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - And Having Writ, 1973 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Black Creation, 1973 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Community of Friends, 3/21/1975 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Synergy of D.C. Anthology, 8/1975 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Black History Museum, 1975 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - B.O.P. (Blacks on Paper), 1975 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Hoo Doo #2, 1975 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Hoo Doo #4, 6.5, 1975-1976 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Janus Collage, 4/1976 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - The Mill, 8/1976 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - The Washingtonian, 9/1976 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Essence, 11/1976 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Caliban, 1976 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Hoo Doo #5, 1976 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Mikrokosmos, 1976 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Obsidian, 1976 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Veins, 1976 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Washout Review, 1976 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Library Journal, 2/1977 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - The Washingtonian, 5/1977 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Cityscape, 6/1977 (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - New Directions, 6/1977 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Jiu-Jitsu, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - The Painted Bride Quarterly, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Proteus, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - NRS, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Ms., 2/1978 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Washingtonian, 5/1978 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Library Journal, 12/1978 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Migrant worker poems by E. Ethelbert Miller, 1978; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 199, Folder 13)
    - review of Lift These Shadows from Our Eyes by Rosemari Mealy, Circa 1978; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 199, Folder 15)
    - Nethula, 1979 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - South and West, 1979 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Twenties in the Sixties, 1979; series 1 subseries 3 (Box 184, Folder 1)
    - The Unrealist, 1979 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Indigene, 1978 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - In Memory of Spirit of Frances, Zara and Lorraine, 1979 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - The Black Scholar, 6/1979 (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Aleph, 1979 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - New Directions, 1975-1987 (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - Hoo Doo #7, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Omowe, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - The Unrealist, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - GW Washington Studies, 5/1981 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - The Nation, 10/3/1981 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Omowe, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Callaloo, 2/1982 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Washington Review, 2/1982 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - New Directions, 7/1982 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Metropolitan Washington, 9/1982 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - The Washingtonian, 11/1982 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - And Not Surrender, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Blind Alleys, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Washington Works, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - Lips, 1983-1984 (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Sojourners, 5/1984 (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Peaceworks, 11/19/1984 (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - Freedomways, 1984 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Montpelier Plus 4, 1984 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - World Words, 1985 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - City Paper, 1/1986 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Reflections, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - poem Billie Holiday, 1986 November 04; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 199, Folder 14)
    - Western Journal of Black Studies, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - American Visions, 4/1987 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - New Directions, 4/1987 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Black American Literature Forum, 1987 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - New Directions, 1/1988 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - The Washington Review, 8/1988 (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - The Black Scholar, 10/1988 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Footwork, 1988 (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - American Visions, 6/1989 (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - Dossier, 11/1989 (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - AWP Chronicle, 12/1989 (Box 55, Folder 16)
    - The Blue Aesthetic (Box 55, Folder 17)
    - The Catalyst (Box 55, Folder 19)
    - Erehwon, 1989 (Box 55, Folder 20)
    - Fear of Others, 1989 (Box 55, Folder 21)
    - New Directions, 1988 (Box 55, Folder 22)
    - Life, 2/1990 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Black Buzzard Review, 1990 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Kanch, 1990 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - New Voices, New Concerns, 1990 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Red Letters, 1990 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Sibanye!, 1990 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - The Chronicle, 1/1991 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Museums and Arts, 5/1991 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - New Voices, New Concerns, 5/1991 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Museum and Arts, 6/1991 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - NAAD (National Association of Artists Organization), 6/1991 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - New Voices, New Concerns, 12/1991 (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - New Directions, 1991 (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Shooting Star, 1991 (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - Sisters (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - The William and Mary Review, 1991 (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - Washington City Paper, 1/1992 (Box 56, Folder 17)
    - Palestine Aid Society, 7th National Convention, 10/1992 (Box 56, Folder 18)
    - Eyeball, 1992 (Box 56, Folder 19)
    - New Essence, 1992 (Box 56, Folder 20)
    - In Search of Color Everywhere, 1993 (Box 56, Folder 21)
    - Stewart Tabori and Chang, 1993 (Box 56, Folder 22)
    - Tailwind, 1993 (Box 56, Folder 23)
    - One, 3/1994 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Callaloo, 1994 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Collisions, 1994 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - The Howard Magazine, 1994 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Sojorners, 3/1995 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Sojorners, 3/1995 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Sojorners, 8/1995 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - G.W. Review, 1995 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Poets & Writers, 5/1994-1/1996 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Ysb, 2/1996 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Black Issues in Higher Education, 3/9/1996 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Sojourners, 5/1996 (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Tribe, 8/1996 (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - Ampersand, 1996 (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - Crab Orchard Review, 1996 (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - Crab Orchard Review, 1997 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Permafrost, 1998 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Progressive, 6/1999 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - American Visions, 7/1999 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Black Issues, 8/1999 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Indigo, 11/1999 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Washington Flyer, 2000 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Black Issues, 2001 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Washington Review, 2001 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - American Writer, 2001-2002 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Howard Magazine, 2002 (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Mosaic, 2002 (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - Spirit of Fire, Faith, Art and Action, 2002 (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - El Comercio, 2003 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Humanities, 2/2003 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Washington Flyer, 8/2003 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - National Book Festival, 10/2003 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - UNLV, 2003 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - The Santa Fe magazine, 10/2004 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Speakeasy, 2004 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Washington Post, 8/2005 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Speakeasy, 2005 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Writers Carousel, 2005 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Peacework, 2006 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Turn the Page and Don't Stop, 2006 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Poets and Writers In Celebration of Writers, 2/27/2007 (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - Master Class and Poetry Reading, 10/10/2007 (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - D.C. North, 1/2008 (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - The Washington Post magazine, 4/27/2008 (Box 59, Folder 16)
    - Fathering Words: reviews, undated (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Features, reviews, 1994-2000 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Interviews, 1992-2007 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Promotional materials, 2008-2009 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Folio, 2000 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Callaloo Volume 22, Number 1, 1999; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - The Black Scholar, Volume 19, Numbers 4 and 5, 1988; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - The Painted Bride Quarterly, Volume 4, Number 1, 1977; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Open Places, Number 41, 1986; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Manoa, Volume 7, Number 1, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Words Cut by a Diamond, Undated; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 174, Folder 4)
    - Publications: Various Works by Ethelbert Miller, n.d., undated; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 144, Folder 3)
    - Publications: Various Works by Ethelbert Miller, 1975-1989; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 144, Folder 4)
    - Publications: Various Works by Ethelbert Miller, 1989-2000; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 144, Folder 5)
    - Publications: Various Works by Ethelbert Miller, 2001-2003; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 144, Folder 6)
    - Publications: Various Works by Ethelbert Miller, 2004-2014; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 145, Folder 1)
    - Publications: Various Works by Ethelbert Miller, Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 161, Folder 1)
    - Publications: Various Works by Ethelbert Miller (1/4), 1976-2014; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 164, Folder 1)
    - Publications: Various Works by Ethelbert Miller (2/4), 1976-2014; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 164, Folder 2)
    - Publications: Various Works by Ethelbert Miller (3/4), 1976-2014; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 164, Folder 3)
    - Publications: Various Works by Ethelbert Miller (4/4), 1976-2014; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 164, Folder 4)
    - Journals featuring Miller, 1972; series 1 subseries 3 (Box 163, Folder 1)
    - Journals featuring Miller, 1972-1978; series 1 subseries 3 (Box 163, Folder 2)
    - Celebrate America in Poetry and in Art, 1994; series 1 subseries 3 (Box 181, Folder 8)
    - Journals featuring Miller, 1995-1996; series 1 subseries 3 (Box 163, Folder 3)
    - Journals featuring Miller, 1997; series 1 subseries 3 (Box 163, Folder 4)
    - African American Review, 2002; series 1 subseries 3 (Box 181, Folder 2)
    - Sheets for Men Only: International Anthology of Poetry and Prose, 2004; series 1 subseries 3 (Box 183, Folder 9)
    - Ebony Magazine, 2010; series 1 subseries 3 (Box 184, Folder 8)
    - The Nation, 2010; series 1 subseries 3 (Box 183, Folder 2)
    - Threshold: A Magazine for the Arts and Sciences, 2010; series 1 subseries 3 (Box 183, Folder 10)
    - Journals featuring Miller, 2004-2011; series 1 subseries 3 (Box 163, Folder 5)
    - Voice Male, 2011-2016; series 1 subseries 3 (Box 184, Folder 3)
    - Howard Magazine, 2011-2012; series 1 subseries 3 (Box 182, Folder 5)
    - Malpais Review, 2012; series 1 subseries 3 (Box 182, Folder 6)
    - Sojourners, 2012; series 1 subseries 3 (Box 183, Folder 8)
    - Midcity DC, 2012-2013; series 1 subseries 3 (Box 182, Folder 7)
    - Revere: Ultra Short Memoirs, 2013; series 1 subseries 3 (Box 183, Folder 7)
    - HillRag, 2013-2014; series 1 subseries 3 (Box 182, Folder 1)
    - HillRag, 2014; series 1 subseries 3 (Box 182, Folder 2)
    - HillRag, 2016; series 1 subseries 3 (Box 182, Folder 4)
    - HillRag, 2014-2015; series 1 subseries 3 (Box 182, Folder 3)
    - African Voices, 2014; series 1 subseries 3 (Box 181, Folder 3)
    - Poets and Writers, 2014; series 1 subseries 3 (Box 183, Folder 6)
    - Urban Voices, 2014; series 1 subseries 3 (Box 184, Folder 2)
    - Washington History, 2014; series 1 subseries 3 (Box 184, Folder 4)
    - Paterson Literary Review, 2014-2015; series 1 subseries 3 (Box 183, Folder 5)
    - Alchemical Vessels, 2015; series 1 subseries 3 (Box 181, Folder 4)
    - Black American Literature Forum, 1980; series 1 subseries 3 (Box 181, Folder 6)
    - Bourgeon, 2013; series 1 subseries 3 (Box 181, Folder 7)
    - DC Live Magazine, 2009; series 1 subseries 3 (Box 181, Folder 9)
    - The Delmarva Review, 2011; series 1 subseries 3 (Box 181, Folder 10)
    - EJ USA, 2014; series 1 subseries 3 (Box 181, Folder 11)
    - HillRag, 2012-2013; series 1 subseries 3 (Box 181, Folder 12)
    - Articles - Clippings, 2009-2012 (Box 181, Folder 1)
    - American Book Review, 2013-2016; series 1 subseries 3 (Box 181, Folder 5)
    - Articles - Clippings, 2005-2016; series 1 subseries 3 (Box 179, Folder 1)
    - The Collected Poems of E. Ethelbert Miller, 2005-2016; series 1 subseries 3 (Box 179, Folder 2)
    - Midcity DC, 2015-2016; series 1 subseries 3 (Box 183, Folder 1)
    - Washingtonian, 2015; series 1 subseries 3 (Box 184, Folder 5)
    - HillRag, 2016; series 1 subseries 3 (Box 179, Folder 3)
    - Nationals Magazine, 2016; series 1 subseries 3 (Box 183, Folder 3)
    - Of Poetry and Protest, 2016; series 1 subseries 3 (Box 183, Folder 4)
    - Sojourners, 2016; series 1 subseries 3 (Box 179, Folder 4)
    - The Writer's Center, 2016; series 1 subseries 3 (Box 184, Folder 6)
    - The Writer's Chronicle, 2016; series 1 subseries 3 (Box 184, Folder 7)
    - Poems, 1987-2004; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 189, Folder 1)
    - Loose Publication Related Documents, 2000-2003; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 189, Folder 2)
    - American Book Review, Volume 40, Number 6, 2019 September-October; MS2215 Series 1 Suberies 3 (Box 200, Folder 10)
    - Copy of "December 31, 1999," published in "Perfect Dragonfly", 2011; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 200, Folder 11)
    - Copies of "Tomorrow," "W.E.B. DuBois," and "Malcom X, August 1952," published in "A Howard Reader.", 1997; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 200, Folder 12)
    - Copies of "Washingtonian" Magazine profiles on Ethelbert Miller, January and February 2018, MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 200, Folder 13)
    - Draft, "When Your Wife has Tommy John Surgery and other Baseball Stories", circa 2021; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 200, Folder 14)
    - Frame on the Walls Sandtown, 2016; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 200, Folder 15)
    - Materials related to "Guns in the Hands of Artists," by Jonathan Ferrara, undated; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 200, Folder 16)
    - Materials related to "A Parallel Road," by Amani Willet, undated; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 200, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous Writings and Correspondence, 1993, 2005, 2011, 2016, undated; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 200, Folder 18)
    - Poet Lore (anniversary editions), MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 200, Folder 19)
    - Poetry and other miscelleanuos writings, 1978, 2010, 2019, 2021, undated; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 200, Folder 20)
    - Quarterly Black Review of Books Volume 2, Number 1, Fall 1994, MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 200, Folder 21)
    - Significant Voices: A Series of Readings and Discussions by 20th Century African American Writers, 2000; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 200, Folder 22)
    - Sojourners, Volume 49, Number 9, September/October 2019, MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 200, Folder 23)
    - Statement and Testimony of E. Ethelbert Miller Before the House Subcomittee on Government Activities and Transportation Review of the Activities of the National Endowment for the Arts, 1991 June 19; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 200, Folder 24)
    - TAB: The Journal of Poetry & Poetics Volume 5, Issue 1 and Volume 6, Issue 1, 2017-2018; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 202, Folder 1)
    - The Writer's Chronicle, 2016 September, 2020 September; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 202, Folder 2)
    - "Voice Male" Magazine, 2014, 2019, 2020-2021; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 202, Folder 3)
    - Washington City Paper "The People Issue", 2021 November; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 202, Folder 4)
    - Writings about E. Ethelbert Miller, 2021, undated; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 202, Folder 5)
    - The Collected Poems of E. Ethelbert Miller, 2016; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 202, Folder 6)
    - Afro American Review, 1969-1970; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 210, Folder 1)
    - AMBIT: A Quarterly of Poems, Short Stories, Drawings, & Criticisms/Contents, 1982; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 210, Folder 2)
    - Before Columbus Foundation: Contemporary American Literature, 1978-1979; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 210, Folder 3)
    - Black Books Bulletin, 1971 Fall; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 210, Folder 4)
    - Black Box 2 and 4, 1972, 1974; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 210, Folder 5)
    - Black Box 4 and 6, 1974, 1975; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 210, Folder 6)
    - Black Box 16 and 17, 1979; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 210, Folder 7)
    - Black Dialogue, 1969; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 210, Folder 8)
    - Black Issues Book Review, 2000 September-October; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 211, Folder 1)
    - Black Theatre: A Periodical of the Black Theatre Movement, 1968-1969, 1971; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 211, Folder 2)
    - "Bubbles," by Eloise Greenfield, 1972; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 211, Folder 3)
    - Doula: The Journal of Rap Music and Hip Hop Culture, circa 2000-2001; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 211, Folder 4)
    - Ebony, 1990, 2008; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 211, Folder 5)
    - Essence, 2008-2009; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 211, Folder 6)
    - First World: An International Journal of Black Thought, 1977; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 211, Folder 7)
    - Hambone, 1987; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 211, Folder 8)
    - Howard University Exhibition catalogs, 1978, 1980, 1986; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 211, Folder 9)
    - NOMMO: The Journal of OBAC Writers' Workshop, 1969; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 212, Folder 1)
    - Race & Class: A Journal For Black and Third World Liberation, 1981; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 212, Folder 2)
    - Rhythm Magazine, 1970; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 212, Folder 3)
    - Ritual & Dissent: A Journal of Afro-American Arts and Letters, 1984; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 212, Folder 4)
    - Sagala: A Journal of Art and Ideas, 1980, 1981, 1984; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 212, Folder 5)
    - Small Press Review [1/2], 1975-1976; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 212, Folder 6)
    - Small Press Review [2/2], 1975-1976; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 212, Folder 7)
    - Spin, 1990, 1992; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 212, Folder 8)
    - Sports Illustrated, 1955 October 10; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 212, Folder 9)
      This issue of Sports Illustrated contains a section on Jackie Robinson and the World Series of 1955. Ethelbert Miller is a longtime baseball fan and has written a number of works related to the sport.
    - The Black Stage Magazine, 1973-1974; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 212, Folder 10)
    - The Feet: The Monthly Black Dance and Arts Magazine, 1973; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 212, Folder 11)
    - The International Book Fair of Radical Black & 3rd World Books, 1982; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 212, Folder 12)
    - "'The Obama Reader,' We Knew Him When: An Inaugural Special From the Chicago Reader", circa 2008-2009; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 212, Folder 13)
  - Works in progress, 1983-2016; Series 1 Subseries 4
    This subseries, dating from 1983-2016, consists of materials that display works in their various stages of development. Included are drafts of Ethelbert Miller's books including the Fifth Inning and On Saturdays I Santana with You as well as personal journals and planners.
    Related Materials
    Researchers interested in E. Ethelbert Miller's notebooks, journals, or planners containing works in progress should check Series 1 Subseries 9. When processing later additions, similar materials were added there and that has been maintained with more subsequent additions.
    - Contracts & Project Ideas, 2015-2016; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 189, Folder 3)